Marya Annette McQuirter Collection 141
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - Dissertation Chapters ( 3 of 3), undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - A Georgetown Childhood 1896-1914 An Oral History Interview, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - The Effect of Course Work in Consumer Buying Upon buying Practices of Negro Students, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Negro Consumer Dissertation, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Government Correspondence, 1935-1946 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Race/Culture/Geography Articles, 1954-1988 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Gender and Culture Artilces, 1994-2005 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Jacqueline Stewart - Dissertation on Black Movies, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - James Brooks - Oral History Interview, 1997-02-12 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Articles - Food Studies, 1993-1998 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - 1930s Newspapers Articles, 1932-1939 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Health and Vegetarianism, 1999-2004 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - VSDC, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Vegfest DC, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Copies of Original Black Vegetarianism Site, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Raw Recipes, undated (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - The Spectrum SIG's Phoenix, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - African Americans and Animals, 1885-2003 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Veg DC - Vegetarianism and Recipes, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Afro American Pamphlets and Newspapers, 1988-2004 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Topeka State Journal and National Survey of African American Museums, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Green Scissors, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Go Go Newspaper Articles, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Department of Justice and Interior Info, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - African American History Articles, 1977-2004 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - 82nd Annual Commencement Howard University, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - DC Voter Guide September 2004 Primary Election (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Misc., 2004-2005 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Clyde's Class Fall 2003, 1999-2004 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - DC Agenda 2003 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - African American Historic Sites Survey and Identification, 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Afro-Americans and the Evolution of A Living Constitution, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Walking with Ella Watson: Using Historical Resources to Tell Stories about D.C's Past, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - UJIMA UMAMAA - Working Together for our Collective Prosperity, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - The African American Heritage Trail Searchable Database, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - O' Write my Name: African American Catholics in the Archdiocese of Washington 1634-1990, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Latin American Dance, undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - DC Rape Crisis Center and Sexual Assault, 1972-1980 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Women Misc, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Woodland Cemetery, undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Howard D. Woodson, undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Workers, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - International Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters/A Philip Randolph, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Hurd v. Dodge, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Langston Hughes, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Charles Houston, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Howard Hall, undated (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Holy Road Cemetery, undated (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Tobias Henson, undated (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Todd Duncan, undated (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - James Wormley, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Washington Conservatory of Music and School of Expression, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - War, 1989-2002 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Paul Laurence Dunbar, undated (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Shiloh Baptist Church, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Shaw, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Segregation, 1918 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Founders Library i, undated (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Robert Flack, undated (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - St. Mary's Episcopal Church, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Benjamin Banneker, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Department Stores, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - General Benjamin Davis, 1965-2002 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Charles Drew, undated (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Dunbar High School/M. St. Prepatory School, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Cemeteries - Misc., 2003 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Central Public Library - City Museum, undated (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Chocolate City, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - City Directory - Misc., 2002 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Theatres Misc., 2002 (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Mary Church and Robert H. Terrell, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - Tenleytown - Misc., 2000 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - Sports, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - Charles Sumner School, undated (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution, undated (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - Patrick Healy, 1988-2003 (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - H Street NE - Misc, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Griffith Stadium, 1924 (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Tudor Place, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - Henry Lincoln Johnson, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - Lois Mailou Jones, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 63)
  - Lewis Jefferson, 1910 (Box 29, Folder 64)
  - Ivy City, 1978-2003 (Box 29, Folder 65)
  - Misc- DC History, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 66)
  - Petworth Misc, 1996-2006 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Guide to Neighborhood Resources, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Petworth Neighborhood Article, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - A History of the Petworth Community, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Petworth History Project, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Petworth History Project, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Petworth History Project Proposal, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Petworth History Project, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Roosevelt High School, 1939-1940 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Humanities Council of DC, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - The United States Soldiers' Home Paul R Goode, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - The Wunder Project and Draft Proposals (1 of 3), 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - The Wunder Project and Draft Proposals (2 of 3), 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - The Wunder Project and Draft Proposals (3 of 3), 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Wunder Project, 1992-1994 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Reports to Board - Wunder Project, 1992-1994 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Financial Reports - Wunder Project, 1992-1994 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Wunder Project Memos and Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Registration Forms, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Consent Forms - Release Forms, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - After School Program and Misc Letters - Wunder Project, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - PTEC Petwroth Tutoring and Enrichment Center, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - AP Building, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Wise Up After School Program Benefits, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Stores for Donations, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Letters, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Funding - Oldies Party, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Grants and Donation Requests, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Computer Information, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Project Coordinator, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Positive Energy Newsletter (1 of 2), 1989-1992 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Positive Energy Newsletter (2 of 2), 1989-1992 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Black Magazines (1 of 5), 1988-1995 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Black Magazines (2 of 5), 1988-1995 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Black Magazines (3 of 5), 1988-1995 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Black Magazines (4 of 5), 1988-1995 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Black Magazines (5 of 5), 1988-1995 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Post Cards/Pamphlets/Brochures, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Bibliography for Black Women's History, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1980-1995 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Newsletters (1 of 3), 1975-1993 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Newsletters (2 of 3), 1975-1993 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Newsletters (3 of 3), 1975-1993 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Journals ( 1 of 2), 1988-1992 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Journals ( 2 of 2), 1988-1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Petworth Summer Youth Academy, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - PTEC - Petworth Tutoring and Enrichment Center: Letters/Newspaper Articles/Certificates, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Community Support Network, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Community Support Network, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Community Support Network, 1992-1996 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Community Support Network Letterhead, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Community Support Network Programs, 1994-2003 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - CSN Statement of Purpose, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - CSN Work Volunteer/Table List, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - USSAH Protocols, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Soldiers Home Contact List, undated (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Suport Network Volunteers, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - CSN Proposla 4/12/99, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Ads for Tutors, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Computers, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Volunteer Hnadbook, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - CSN and Wunder Project Pamphlets, 1992-1998 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Parent Handbook, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Wunder Project Memos, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Reciept Books, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - By Laws - Wise Up Inc., 1992 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Wise UP Newsletter, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Student Newspapers, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Facilities Usage Agreement, undated (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Children's Books, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Business Development - The After School Program and Enviornmental Enhancement, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Reading Club, 1996-2000 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - By Laws - Articles of Incorporation, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - The Jarvis Challenge Business Improvemet Project, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Petworth Tutoring and Enrichment Cetner Info and Articles, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Reading Club Schedules, 1993-1996 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Neighborhood Newspaper Articles, 1994-1998 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - CSN Quilting Club, 1996-2001 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Address List for Mailing, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - CSN Computer Education, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Student Addresses and Telephone, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Reading Club: Awards/Calendars/Registration forms, 1993-1996 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Student Sign in/Sign Out Sheet, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Reciepts, 1995-1997 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - CSN Letters, 1993-2000 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - CSN Donation Letters, 1993-1998 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Index Cards, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Frank Leslies Illustrated Poster, 1861 (Box 36, Folder 2)